# PÉTER JÓZSA

**FULL STACK DEVELOPER** 





### CODECOOL

### **Contact**

jozsa.peter88@gmail.com

**%** +36202914145

www.linkedin.com/in/

peterjozsa98/

github.com/jozsapeter88

### **Self Definition**

I'm a driven and ambitious person with a strong passion for technology and a desire to set foot in the IT industry. During my studies at Codecool, I had the opportunity to gain valuable experience in teamwork and collaboration. Working closely with my peers and mentors, I actively engaged in group projects that required effective communication, coordination, and problemsolving skills. Outside of my professional pursuits, you can often find me actively participating in various sports activities and following the world of technological advances.

## Strength

I have experience in developing full-stack applications and I feel my main strength in expressing creativity on the frontend side. I also have experience in Git version control, Docker, CI/CD and databases. Communication and teamwork are strong suits of mine, and I welcome constructive criticism as an opportunity for growth. Continuously learning and staying updated with industry advancements are essential to me.

## **Mentor Opinion**

"Péter consistently delivered a good quality work during his time at Codecool. He is willing to ask questions and open for feedback to improve his skills. He is extremely reliable: have not even been late once during his entire year. His teammates enjoy working with him. He will be a solid member of any software developer team as a junior, and will grow rapidly to medior level."

- Kornél Regius, mentor



### **Hard Skills**



























## **Recent Projects**

#### STOCK MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

#### https://github.com/jozsapeter88/stock-manager

A React/C# project that helps manage facilities and track their corresponding item stock.

#### STOCK MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

#### https://github.com/jozsapeter88/Goal.NET

A football fantasy-team-themed project in an ASP.NET environment with C# on the backend and React on the frontend.

#### PERSONAL PORTFOLIO

#### https://github.com/jozsapeter88/personal-portfolio

A site made to introduce myself, highlight my works and practice my React and CSS(Sass) skills.

## **Work Experience**

Customer Service Associate (2019 - 2020) — MediaMarkt Magyarország Courier (2020 - 2023) — Wolt Freelancer Translator (2017 - 2023) — Translator

### **Education**

**Mechatronics preparatory training** (2013 - 2017) — DSZC Brassai Sámuel Grammar School and Technical High School

**Mechatronics trechnician training** (2017 - 2018) — DSZC Brassai Sámuel Grammar School and Technical High School

**BA in English and American Studies** (2018 - 2021) — University of Debrecen **Full-Stack Development Course** (2022 - 2023) — Codecool

### Spoken Languages

English — Advanced Spanish — Intermediate

